const PronounQuestion =[
    {
        question: "What is a pronoun??",
        options: ["A word that modifies a noun", " A word that expresses action or state of being ", "A word that takes the place of a noun", "A word that connects phrases or clauses"],
        correct_option: "A word that takes the place of a noun"
      },
      {
        question: "Identify the pronoun in the sentence: She gave him the book.?",
        options: ["She", " Him ", "Give", "book"],
        correct_option: "Him"
      },
      {
        question: "Choose  correct pronoun to complete the sentence: John and ___ went to the store?",
        options: ["Me", " I ", "Myself", "My"],
        correct_option: "I"
      },
      {
        question: "In the sentence They are waiting for us, what is the pronoun?",
        options: ["They", " Are ", "Waiting", "Us"],
        correct_option: "They"
      },
      {
        question: "Select the pronoun from the options:?",
        options: ["Run", " He ", "Quickly", "Happy"],
        correct_option: "He"
      },
      {
        question: "Identify the pronoun in the sentence: We will go to the party.?",
        options: ["Will", " We ", "Go", "Party"],
        correct_option: "We"
      },
      {
        question: "Which word in the sentence is NOT a pronoun: She sings beautifully.?",
        options: ["She", " Sing ", "Beautifully", "None of these"],
        correct_option: "Beautifully"
      },
      {
        question: "What pronoun is used to refer to a group of people?",
        options: ["He", " She ", "They", "It"],
        correct_option: "They"
      },
      {
        question: "In the sentence: I love you. what is the pronoun?",
        options: ["I", "love  ", "You", "None of these"],
        correct_option: "I"
      },
      {
        question: "Choose the correct pronoun to complete the sentence: ___ is a good friend.?",
        options: ["She", "Happy  ", "Quickly", "It"],
        correct_option: "She"
      },




];
export default PronounQuestion;